{
    "question": "Tulislahlah 100 kata benda (noun) lengkap dengan artinya!",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "\u2013 account \u2013 artinya: rekening, akun <br> \u2013 achiever \u2013 yang berprestasi <br> \u2013 acoustics \u2013 akustik <br> \u2013 action \u2013 tindakan <br> \u2013 activity \u2013 aktivitas <br> \u2013 actor \u2013 aktor, bintang film untuk laki <br> \u2013 addition \u2013 tambahan <br> \u2013 adjustment \u2013 pengaturan <br> \u2013 advertisement \u2013 iklan <br> \u2013 advice \u2013 nasihat <br> \u2013 aftermath \u2013 buntut <br> \u2013 afternoon \u2013 sore <br> \u2013 afterthought \u2013 renungan <br> \u2013 agreement \u2013 perjanjian <br> \u2013 air \u2013 udara <br> \u2013 airplane \u2013 pesawat terbang <br> \u2013 airport \u2013 bandara <br> \u2013 alarm \u2013 alarm <br> \u2013 alley \u2013 gang <br> \u2013 amount \u2013 jumlah <br> \u2013 amusement \u2013 hiburan <br> \u2013 anger \u2013 kemarahan <br> \u2013 angle \u2013 sudut <br> \u2013 animal \u2013 hewan <br> \u2013 answer adalah kata benda (noun) dalam bahasa Inggris berarti: jawaban<br>- ant \u2013 artinya: semut <br> \u2013 ants \u2013 banyak semut<br> \u2013 apparatus \u2013 aparat <br> \u2013 apparel \u2013 pakaian <br> \u2013 apple \u2013 apel <br> \u2013 apples \u2013 apel bentuk jamak<br> \u2013 appliance \u2013 alat <br> \u2013 approval \u2013 persetujuan <br> \u2013 arch \u2013 lengkungan <br> \u2013 argument \u2013 argumen <br> \u2013 arithmetic \u2013 hitungan<br> \u2013 arm \u2013 lengan <br> \u2013 army \u2013 tentara <br> \u2013 art \u2013 seni <br> \u2013 attack \u2013 serangan<br> \u2013 attempt \u2013 usaha <br> \u2013 attention \u2013 perhatian <br> \u2013 attraction \u2013 daya tarik <br> \u2013 aunt \u2013 bibi <br> \u2013 authority \u2013 kewenangan <br> \u2013 babies \u2013 bayi <br> \u2013 baby \u2013 bayi <br> \u2013 back \u2013 kembali <br> \u2013 badge \u2013 lencana <br> \u2013 bag adalah kata benda (noun) dalam bahasa Inggris berarti: tas<br>- bait \u2013 artinya: umpan <br> \u2013 balance \u2013 keseimbangan<br> \u2013 ball \u2013 bola <br> \u2013 balloon \u2013 balon <br> \u2013 balls \u2013 bola <br> \u2013 banana \u2013 pisang <br> \u2013 band \u2013 pita <br> \u2013 base \u2013 dasar <br> \u2013 baseball \u2013 baseball <br> \u2013 basin \u2013 cekungan <br> \u2013 basket \u2013 keranjang <br> \u2013 basketball \u2013 bola basket <br> \u2013 bat \u2013 kelelawar <br> \u2013 bath \u2013 mandi <br> \u2013 battle \u2013 pertempuran <br> \u2013 bead \u2013 titis <br> \u2013 beam \u2013 balok <br> \u2013 bean \u2013 kacang <br> \u2013 bear \u2013 beruang <br> \u2013 bears \u2013 beruang <br> \u2013 beast \u2013 binatang <br> \u2013 bed \u2013 tempat tidur <br> \u2013 bedroom \u2013 kamar tidur <br> \u2013 beds \u2013 ranjang <br> \u2013 bee adalah kata benda (noun) dalam bahasa Inggris berarti: lebah <br><br><br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "book=buku<br>table=meja<br>chair=kursi<br>pillow=bantal<br>knife=pisau<br>cupboard=lemari<br>desk=meja belajar<br>door=pintu<br>eraser=penghapus<br>pencil=pensil<br>pen=pulpen<br>marker=spidol<br>whiteboard=papan tulis putih<br>blackboard=papan tulis hitam<br>window=jendela<br>apple=apel<br>bike=sepeda<br>bed=kasur<br>flag=bendela<br>board=papan<br>wood=kayu<br>pencil case=tempat pensil<br>bag=tas<br>pouch=tas kecil<br>shoe=sepatu<br>sandals=sandal<br>computer=komputer<br>paper=kertas<br>floor=lantai<br>cloth=baju<br>skirt=rok<br>short=celana pendek<br>trouser=celana panjang<br>trash=tempat sampah<br>crap=sampah<br>dust=debu<br>wardrobe=tempat baju<br>map=peta<br>globe=bola dunia<br>clock=jam<br>wall=tembok<br>fence=pagar<br>blanket=selimut<br>aduh apa itu udah 100?capek ngetik nih",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-active-passive-pd-present-perfect-past-perfect-f-733",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat active passive pd present perfect, past perfect, future present, future past!:)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Present\nPerfect Tense\n<br>\n- Active : I\nhave called my best friend<br>- Passive :\nI have been called by my best friend\n\n<br>Past\nPerfect Tense<br>- Active : I\nhad called my best friend\n<br>\n- Passive :\nI had been called by my best friend\n<br>\nSimple\nFuture Tense<br>- Active : I\nshall call my best friend\n<br>\n- Passive :\nI shall be call by called by my best friend<br>\u00a0Future Past\nTense<br>\u00a0- Active : I\nshould call my best friend<br>\u00a0- Passive :\nI should be called by my best friend\n\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "cara-cepet-biar-bisa-bahasa-inggris-801",
            "question": "Cara cepet biar bisa bahasa inggris ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "caranya adalah : kamu harus suka dulu guru dan pelajarannya.\nkanu harus sering menonton film barat\nkamu harus sering mendengar argumen bahasa inggria",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "les inggris.....sering baca artikel bhs.inggris....pelajari bahasa ingris....main game yang bahasa inggris.....lihat video pengetahuan tentang bahasa ingrris",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "yang-benar-we-did-an-opening-ceremony-atau-we-did-the-opening-cer-713",
            "question": "Yang benar we did an opening ceremony atau we did the opening ceremony?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "we did the opening ceremony\u00a0<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "we did the opening ceremony..",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-6-orang-di-dalam-hotel-dalam-bahasa-inggris-502",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan 6 orang di dalam hotel dalam bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Receptionist: Good morning! Welcome to Cozy Hotel. Could I help you?<br>Mr. John : Good morning! I&#039;d like to book a room for several days, please<br>Receptionist: Sure. How many days would you like to stay?<br>Mrs. John : 3 days and 2 nights, please<br>Receptionist : Certainly. We&#039;ve got room 145, 209, 310 for free. which one do you prefer?<br>Lily: Dad, I think I prefer room 310<br>Dave: Me too, dad<br>Mr. john: ok, then we&#039;d like to book room 310, please<br>Receptionist: Certainly, sir. How are you going to be paying?<br>Mrs. John: Credit card, please<br>Receptionist: Sure. Is there anything else we could help?<br>Mr. John: I think we need someone to help us bring our luggage<br>Receptionist: Sure. We&#039;ve got bellboy to help you<br>Bellboy: Good morning! <br>Mrs &amp; Mr John: Good morning! Could you help us with our luggage to room 310<br>Bellboy: Sure.<br>Receptionist: We hope you&#039;ll enjoy your stay here<br>Mrs. John: We hope so. Thank you<br>Receptionist: Your welcome<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-tentang-memberi-komentar-terhadap-berita-dalam-bhs-148",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat tentang memberi komentar terhadap berita dalam bhs inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "i like that news, but i think .....",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pelajaran-bahasa-inggris-unit-6-kurikulum-2013-activity-9-dan-282",
            "question": "Pelajaran bahasa inggris, unit 6, kurikulum 2013, activity 9 dan activity 10",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A : hello Dewi. Is kaisar here?<br>B : No. i\u2019m afraid he go\u00a0out\u00a0<br>A : oh, what a pity ! when exactly does he go<br><span>B : about fifteen minutes ago<br></span><br>2. A : your hair looks different. do you have a haircut?\u00a0<br>B : yes, i have<br>A : do you cut it yourself?\u00a0<br><span>B : no, kadita cut it for me\u00a0<br></span><br>Klo salah maaf atau kamu\u00a0udah bisa jawab ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apakah-artinya-lapangan-sepak-bola-dalam-bahasa-inggris-313",
            "question": "Apakah artinya lapangan sepak bola dalam bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>football field</span> jawabanya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "football field : lapangan sepak bola",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jelaskan-dan-berikan-contoh-verbnounadjectiveand-adverbs-933",
            "question": "Jelaskan dan berikan contoh verb,noun,adjective,and adverbs",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><span>\"Joe ate his\u00a0banana.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0noun</span><span><span>\"They\u00a0ran\u00a0all the way home.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0verb</span><span><span>\"You are a\u00a0pretty\u00a0girl.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0adjective</span><span><span>\"He\u00a0quietly\u00a0opened the door.\"</span>\u00a0-\u00a0<span>adverb</span></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "verb : kata kerja contoh : sitdown,stand up,laughing<br>noun : kata benda conntoh : chair,pencilcase<br>adverb : kata keterangan contoh : now,yesterday,tomorrow<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "develop-the-following-sentences-with-adverbs-of-mannerplace-and-204",
            "question": "Develop The following sentences with adverbs of manner,place and time \u00a0 1.The ant worked 2.The crow ate a piece of meat 3.The rabbit ran 4.The wind blew 5.the girl was carrying a pail of milk 6. the dog was walking 7.the stork drank 8.the tiger killed a lamb",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1) the ant worked hard together to reach their place<br>2) the crow ate a piece of meat and it flew away<br>3) the rabbit ran quickly through this way yesterday<br>4) the wind blew softly in my place last night<br>6) the girl was carrying a pail of milk and walked to her home<br>7) the stork drank the water from the lake\u00a0<br>8) the tiger killed a lamb to have lunc in a farm<br><br><strong>semoga membantu^^</strong><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kalau-nama-lain-dari-v1-v2-v3-dan-ving-apa-701",
            "question": "Kalau nama lain dari V1, V2, V3, dan Ving apa?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "v1 : bare infintive<br>v2 : past tense<br>v3: past participle<br>ve/es : additional infinitive<br>ving : present participle<br><br>maksudnya ini ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}